<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<addon id="metadata.artists.metal-archives.com"
       name="Encyclopaedia Metallum"
       version="1.0.1"
       provider-name="spiff">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.metadata" version="1.0"/>
    <import addon="metadata.common.htbackdrops.com" version="1.0.1"/>
    <import addon="metadata.common.last.fm" version="1.0.1"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.metadata.scraper.artists"
             language="en"
             library="metal-archives.xml"/>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary>Download information about your metal from Encyclopaedia Metallum</summary>
    <summary lang="hu">Encyclopaedia Metallum Zene scraper</summary>
    <description>Encyclopaedia Metallum: The Metal Archives is a website which lists bands from various forms of heavy metal music.

Encyclopaedia Metallum attempts to provide comprehensive information on each band, such as a discography, logos, pictures, lyrics, line-ups, biography, trivia and user-submitted reviews.

The site also provides a system for submitting bands to the archives, and users are encouraged to use it. The site has 73,000+ bands listed, 170,000+ releases, 1,196,000+ tracks, 52,000+ reviews and 227,000+ registered users. It is one of the top 500 most-visited websites in five countries.</description>
    <description lang="hu">A Metal Archives egy weboldal ami a heavy metal zene különböző formáit listázza.
Az oldal megpróbál olyan átfogó információkat nyújtani minden egyes csapatról, mint a diszkográfia, logók, képek, dalszövegek, felállások, életrajzok és felhasználói vélemények.
Továbbá egy olyan rendszert nyújt melyben a felhasználók bátorítva vannak, hogy együtteseket, információkat adjanak hozzá az adatbázishoz. Az oldalon 73,000+ együttes van listázva, 1,196,000+ szám, 52,000+ kritika és 227,000+ regisztrált felhasználó. A webhely benne van az 500 leglátogatottabb weboldal között öt országban.</description>
    <platform>all</platform>
  </extension>
</addon>
