<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<addon id="metadata.universal"
       name="Universal Movie Scraper"
       version="2.4.3"
       provider-name="Olympia, Team XBMC">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.metadata" version="2.1.0"/>
    <import addon="metadata.common.themoviedb.org" version="2.9.0"/>
    <import addon="metadata.common.movieposterdb.com" version="1.0.5"/>
    <import addon="metadata.common.imdb.com" version="2.7.0"/>
    <import addon="metadata.common.impa.com" version="1.0.3"/>
    <import addon="metadata.common.hdtrailers.net" version="1.0.7"/>
    <import addon="metadata.common.youtubetrailers" version="1.0.4"/>
    <import addon="metadata.common.rt.com" version="1.4.0"/>
    <import addon="metadata.common.ofdb.de" version="1.0.0"/>
    <import addon="metadata.common.trakt.tv" version="1.0.0"/>
    <import addon="metadata.common.port.hu" version="1.0.0"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.metadata.scraper.movies"
             language="en"
             library="universal.xml"/>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary lang="af">Universele Fliek Skraper</summary>
    <summary lang="be">Universal Movie Scraper</summary>
    <summary lang="bg">Универсален източник на инф. за филми</summary>
    <summary lang="ca">Buscador Universal de Pel·licules</summary>
    <summary lang="cs">Univerzální zdroj dat k filmům</summary>
    <summary lang="cy">Crafwr Ffilmiau Cyffredinol</summary>
    <summary lang="da">Universal Film-scraper</summary>
    <summary lang="de">Universal Movie Scraper</summary>
    <summary lang="el">Universal Scraper Ταινιών</summary>
    <summary lang="en">Universal Movie Scraper</summary>
    <summary lang="es">Buscador Universal de Películas</summary>
    <summary lang="es_AR">Buscador Universal de Películas</summary>
    <summary lang="et">Universaalne filmide kraabits</summary>
    <summary lang="fr">Collecteur de films universel</summary>
    <summary lang="gl">Scraper universal de filmes</summary>
    <summary lang="he">סקרייפר סרטים אוניברסלי</summary>
    <summary lang="hu">Univerzális film adat leolvasó</summary>
    <summary lang="it">Scraper universale di film</summary>
    <summary lang="ja">万能映画スクレーパー</summary>
    <summary lang="ko">Universal 영화 자료수집기</summary>
    <summary lang="mk">Universal Movie Scraper</summary>
    <summary lang="my">Universal Movie Scraper</summary>
    <summary lang="nl">Universele filmscraper</summary>
    <summary lang="no">Universal Film Scraper</summary>
    <summary lang="pl">Universal Movie Scraper</summary>
    <summary lang="pt">Scraper Universal de Filmes</summary>
    <summary lang="pt_BR">Scraper de FIlmes Universal</summary>
    <summary lang="ro">Catalog de filme universal</summary>
    <summary lang="ru">Универсальный скрапер фильмов</summary>
    <summary lang="sk">Univerzálny sťahovač pre filmy</summary>
    <summary lang="sl">Univerzalni ponudnik informacij o filmih</summary>
    <summary lang="sv">Universell filmskrapa</summary>
    <summary lang="ta_IN">ஒட்டு மொத்தமான நிகழ்படம் சுரண்டி</summary>
    <summary lang="th">Universal Movie Scraper</summary>
    <summary lang="vi">Trình lấy dữ liệu phim ảnh Universal Scraper</summary>
    <summary lang="zh">通用电影刮削器</summary>
    <summary lang="zh_TW">通用的電影資訊搜括器</summary>
    <description lang="af">Hierdie skraper kollekteer inligting van die volgende ondersteunde werwe: IMDb, TMDb, Rotten Tomatoes, Trakt.tv, OFDb.de. Dit doen altyd die aanvanklike soektog op TMDb, maar daarna kan dit veld vir veld gestel word vanaf watter werf jy die spesifieke inligting wil hê.</description>
    <description lang="be">This scraper collecting information from the following supported sites: IMDb, TMDb, Rotten Tomatoes, Trakt.tv, OFDb.de. It always does the initial search on TMDb, but following that it can be set field by field that from which site you want that specific information.</description>
    <description lang="bg">Сваля информация от следните сайтове: IMDb, TMDb, Rotten Tomatoes, Trakt.tv, OFDb.de. Можете да определите от кой сайт каква информация да се сваля.&#10;&#10;Първоначалното търсене винаги се прави в TMDb.</description>
    <description lang="cs">Univerzální zdroj dat, který získává informace z následujících podporovaných stránek: IMDb, TMDb, Rotten Tomatoes, Trakt.tv, OFDb.de, port.hu. Vždy provádí základní hledání na TMDb či IMDb (podle nastavení), ale pro následující hledání může být upraveno pro každou hodnotu, ze které stránky chcete specifickou informaci získat.</description>
    <description lang="cy">Universal Scraper yw'r crafwr mwyaf cyfaddas ar hyn o bryd drwy gasglu gwybodaeth o'r gwefannau canlynol: IMDb, TMDb, Rotten Tomatoes, Trakt.tv, OFDb.de, port.hu. Y crafwr hwn yw'r prif crafwr Team-XBMC. Mae modd gwneud y chwilio cyntaf un ai ar TMDb neu IMDb (yn ôl y gosodiadau) ac ar ôl hynny gall ei osod yn ôl maes o ba wefan i gasglu'r wybodaeth benodol.</description>
    <description lang="da">Denne scraper indsamler information fra følgende understøttede sider: IMDb, TMDb, Rotten Tomatoes, Trakt.tv, OFDb.de. Første søgning sker altid i TMDb, men efterfølgende kan der felt for felt vælges, hvilken side den specifikke infomation ønskes fra.</description>
    <description lang="de">Dieser Sammler sammelt Informationen von den folgenden, unterstützten Seiten: IMDb, TMDb, Rotten Tomatoes, Trakt.tv, OFDb.de. Es fürt jedes mal die Anfangssuche auf TMDb aus, aber danach kann Feld für Feld ausgewählt werden, woher die Informationen geholt werden sollen.</description>
    <description lang="el">Αυτό το scraper συλλέγει πληροφορίες από τις ακόλουθες ιστοσελίδες: IMDb, TMDb, Rotten Tomatoes, Trakt.tv, OFDb.de. Η αρχική αναζήτηση γίνεται πάντα στο TMDb, αλλά έπειτα μπορεί να ρυθμιστεί πεδίο ανά πεδίο από ποια σελίδα να λαμβάνονται πληροφορίες.</description>
    <description lang="en">Universal Scraper is currently the most customizable scraper by collecting information from the following supported sites: IMDb, TMDb, Rotten Tomatoes, Trakt.tv, OFDb.de, port.hu. This scraper is currently the flagship of the Team-XBMC scrapers. The initial search can be done either on TMDb or IMDb (according to the settings), but following that it can be set field by field that from which site you want that specific information.</description>
    <description lang="es">Este buscador obtiene información de los siguientes sitios: IMDb, TMDb, Rotten Tomatoes, Trakt.tv, OFDb.de. La primera búsqueda siempre se realiza en TMDb, pero se puede elegir, campo por campo, de qué sitio se tiene que obtener la información.</description>
    <description lang="es_AR">Este buscador obtiene información de los siguientes sitios: IMDb, TMDb, Rotten tomatoes, Trakt.tv, OFDb.de. Realiza la búsqueda inicial en TMDb, pero a partir de allí se puede especificar desde que sitio se desea obtener cada campo.</description>
    <description lang="fr">Ce scraper collecte les informations depuis les sites supportés suivants : IMDb, TMDb, Rotten Tomatoes, Trakt.tv, OFDb.de. La recherche initiale est toujours effectuée depuis TMDb, mais vous pouvez indiquer les sites sources des champs un par un pour avoir une information plus spécifique.</description>
    <description lang="gl">O Scraper Universal é na actualidade o máis personalizábel en canto a obtención de información dos seguintes sitio: IMDb, TMDb, Rotten Tomatoes, Trakt.tv, OFDb.de, port.hu. Este scraper é actualmente o barco insignia dos scrapers de do equipo de XBMC. A busca inicial pódese realizar ben sexa en TMDb ou IMDb (dependendo da configuración), pero despois de especificar campo a campo dende que sitio desexa esa información específica.</description>
    <description lang="he">סקרייפר זה אוסף מידע מהתארים הנתמכים הבאים: IMDb, TMDb, Rotten Tomatoes, Trakt.tv, OFDb.de זה תמיד עושה את החיפוש הפנימי ב-TMDb, אבל בהתאם לזאת ניתן להגדיר לכל שדה מאיזה אתר אתה רוצה לקבל את המידע.</description>
    <description lang="hu">Ez a leolvasó a következő helyekről gyűjt információkat: IMDb, TMDb, Rotten Tomatoes, Trakt.tv, OFDb.de. A kezdő keresést midig az IMDb-n végzi, de utána mezőnként beállítható, hogy melyik oldalakat használja az adott információ lekérésére.</description>
    <description lang="it">Lo Scraper Universale è al momento lo scraper più personalizzabile, raccogliendo le informazioni dai seguenti siti: IMDb, TMDb, Rotten Tomatoes, Trakt.tv, OFDb.de, port.hu. Questo scraper è il migliore tra gli scraper del Team-XBMC. La ricerca iniziale può essere eseguita sia su TMDb che su IMDb (a seconda delle impostazioni), ma per le successive informazioni è possibile impostare un sito per ogni campo di informazione preciso da raccogliere.</description>
    <description lang="ja">このスクレーパーは、以下のサイトから情報を取得します。IMDb、TMDb、Rotten Tomatoes、Trakt.tv、OFDb.de。最初の検索は TMDb から行われますが、それに続く検索は各フィールドごとにどのサイトで検索するか設定できます。</description>
    <description lang="ko">이 영화 자료수집기는 IMDb, TMDb, Rotten Tomatoes, Trakt.tv, OFDb.de에서 영화 정보를 가져옵니다. 초기 설정은 TMDb에서 검색하지만 특정 정보는 지정한 사이트에서 가져오도록 필드별 설정이 가능합니다.</description>
    <description lang="mk">This scraper collecting information from the following supported sites: IMDb, TMDb, Rotten Tomatoes, Trakt.tv, OFDb.de. It always does the initial search on TMDb, but following that it can be set field by field that from which site you want that specific information.</description>
    <description lang="nl">Deze scraper verzamelt informatie van de volgende ondersteunde sites: IMDb, TMDb, Rotten Tomatoes, Trakt.tv, OFDb.de. Het start altijd de eerste zoektocht op TMDb, maar vervolgens kan veld voor veld informatie gekozen worden van de site waar jij de specifieke informatie van wilt.</description>
    <description lang="no">Denne scraper samler inn informasjon fra følgende støttede steder:  IMDb, TMDb, Rotten Tomatoes, Trakt.tv, OFDb.de, port.hu. På nåværende tidspunkt er denne scraperen flaggskipet blant Team-XBMC scrapere. Første søk skjer alltid i TMDb eller IMDb (avhengig av innstillinger). I etterfølgende søk kan det derimot velges felt for felt hvilken side den spesifikke informasjonen ønskes fra.</description>
    <description lang="pl">Ten scraper zbiera informacje z następujących portali: IMDb, TMDb, Rotten Tomatoes, Trakt.tv, OFDb.de. Najpierw szuka na TMDb, a następnie może być ustawiony by poszczególne pola były wypełnione informacjami z innych portali.</description>
    <description lang="pt">O Universal Scraper é, actualmente, o mais configurável dos scrapers, que recolhe informação dos seguintes sítios: IMDb, TMDb, Rotten Tomatoes, Trakt.tv, OFDb.de, port.hu. Este é, neste momento, o topo de gama dos scrapers da Team-XBMC. A pesquisa inicial pode ser feita no TMDb ou no IMDb (de acordo com as definições), mas depois pode especificar para cada campo os sítios a partir dos quais quer obter informação.</description>
    <description lang="pt_BR">Este scraper coleta informações dos seguintes sites: IMDb, TMDb, Rotten Tomatoes, Trakt.tv, OFDb.de. A busca inicial sempre se dá no TMDb, mas segue aquilo que estiver setado campo a campo  dos sites que você deseja informação específica.</description>
    <description lang="ro">Acest catalog este completat cu informații de la următoarele siteuri: IMDb, TMDb, Rotten Tomatoes, Trakt.tv, OFDb.de. Căutarea inițială se face întotdeauna pe TMDb, dar după aceasta fiecare câmp poate fi setat să ia informația de pe un site specific.</description>
    <description lang="ru">Этот модуль собирает информацию со следующих поддерживаемых сайтов: IMDb, TMDb, Rotten Tomatoes, Trakt.tv, OFDb.de. Он всегда делает начальный поиск по TMDb, хотя может быть установлена последовательность того, с какого сайта Вы хотите получить конкретную информацию.</description>
    <description lang="sk">Tento sťahovač zbiera informácie z týchto stránok: IMDb, TMDb, Rotten Tomatoes, Trakt.tv, OFDb.de. Počiatočné vyhľadávanie vždy robí pomocou TMDb, ale následne môžete pole po poli nastaviť z ktorej stránky má zbierať špecifické informácie. </description>
    <description lang="sl">Ta ponudnik združuje informacije s sledečih strani: IMDb, TMDb, Rotten Tomatoes, Trakt.tv, OFDb.de. Vedno opravi osnovno iskanje na TMDb, vendar lahko nastavite od kod se bo prenesla posamezna informacija.</description>
    <description lang="sv">Denna skrapa samlar information från följande siter: IMDb, RMDb, Rotten Tomatoes, Trakt.tv, OFDb.de. Sökning görs alltid först på TMDb, men den kan konfigureras att hämta efterföljande information - fält för fält - från valfri site.</description>
    <description lang="ta_IN">உலகளாவிய சுரண்டி தற்போது பின்வரும் ஆதரவு தளங்களில் இருந்து தகவல்களை சேகரித்து உள்ளது: IMDb, TMDb, Rotten Tomatoes, Trakt.tv, OFDb.de, port.hu. ஆரம்ப தேடலானது, TMDb அல்லது IMDb (அமைப்புகளை பொறுத்து) செய்யலாம், அதன் பின்னர் உங்களுக்கு தேவையான குறிப்பிட்ட தகவல்களை அமைப்பு செய்து கொள்ள முடியும்.</description>
    <description lang="th">การดึงข้อมูลภาพยนตร์ได้รับการสนับสนุนจากเว็บไซต์  IMDb, TMDb, Rotten Tomatoes, Trakt.tv, OFDb.de. โดยจะดึงข้อมูลจากเว็บ TMDB เป็นอันดับแรก แต่คุณสามารถตั้งค่าการรับข้อมูลจากเว็บไซต์ที่คุณต้องการได้</description>
    <description lang="vi">Trình Universal Scraper là trình thu thập thông tin được với khả năng tuỳ biến tốt nhất, hỗ trợ thu thập thông tin từ các site: IMDb, TMDb, Rotten Tomatoes, Trakt.tv, OFDb.de, port.hu. Trình này hiện là công cụ thu thập chuẩn nổi bật nhất của Team-XBMC. Việc tìm kiếm ban đầu có thể thực hiện ở cả 2 site TMDb hay IMDb (tuỳ thiết lập của bạn), kế tiếp sẽ do người dùng tuỳ chỉnh các thông tin cụ thể được lựa chọn từ từng site</description>
    <description lang="zh">本刮削器从以下站点获取信息：IMDb、TMDb、Rotten Tomatoes、Trakt.tv、OFDb.de。初始结果总是先从TMDb获取，然后可以针对不同项目分别设置从不同站点获取信息。</description>
    <description lang="zh_TW">Universal Scraper是現今可客製化程度最高的搜括器，並從以下的支援網站取得資訊：IMDb, TMDb, Rotten Tomatoes, Trakt.tv, OFDb.de。這​​是目前XBMC團隊的旗艦搜括器。它總以 TMDb或IMDB (根據設定值) 當作初始搜尋的網站，但可以單獨在每一個獨立的選項設定你要得網站並取得指定的相關資訊。</description>
    <platform>all</platform>
  </extension>
</addon>
